Did you see the season's new anime?
Of course.
What will you keep watching?
Not this game.
Clearly, I am no match for you.
Five in a row - Laozi wins
Thank you for the game, Emperor Yan.
By the way...
Is it true that the Sky Pearl was stolen?
Your spirit parts?
I've sent them up the hill.
Don't we go there now?
The nearby hills are not suitable for Piyu.
Today we will go deeper.
All right, let's go.
Piyu!
Come here!
Where will we release him?
In a place with no people.
Won't other animals hurt him?
Don't worry, Xiaohei is the only one who can catch him.
Isn't Piyu fond of wood?
What if he eats up the whole forest?
Trees too are living things.
They become wood when they die.
Piyu won't eat living trees.
Deep in the Mountains
And now, today's weather.
Typhoon "Show Joy" is approaching the village.
Be sure to take the laundry in!
Again?
When exactly?
It is not confirmed as of now.
Most likely in two episodes' time.
Now I go tell the other households.
The kids better hurry.
From here we have to go by foot.
Careful!
Looks like no one's been around here for a long time.
Yeah, this has been Grandpa's wood gathering trail.
Wow...
So many fairies!
Beautiful, huh?
It's not shy of me!
Yeah.
The villagers don't hurt them, do they?
No.
We are getting along with them.
This is the place.
Beyond this rock lies their world.
We can't go any further.
What a huge rock...
Who put it here?
I don't know...
Piyu!
We can't go in there with you.
It's time to say goodbye.
You are free now.
Don't go to people's houses again!
Come!
We can't go...
Race to the top?
Sure!
Piyu!
Why... Why are you crying now?
Won't he be lonely in the forest?
I don't know...
What if he'll be starving?
It can't happen.
Will he think about us sometimes?
Maybe...
The sky turned quite dark...
The forecast said a big rainfall is coming.
Won't Piyu be in danger?
He'll be alright.
Grandpa!
Take Xiaobai in the house!
Do you feel it too?
A strong spirit aura...
Diting...?
Who is it?
I think it's a spirit.
Wow...
Humans?
Do you want to fight me?
Fighting!
I am the king of fighting!
I will be back!
How could you find this place?
I've simply followed the strongest aura around.
Strange... Xiaohei's aura must be quite weak now...
The strongest
around
↗
Hand the Pearl over, right now.
He can't do it right now.
Grandpa!
Why?
Because the episode is over.
I see I'm no match for you.
Give up the Pearl!
I've told you already.
Ask Master Lao, he knows it all.
Why would I trust you?
Did you get him?
Yeah, sure.
Diting
It was before you became the master's disciple.
If you can't trust me, I'll go to him with you.
Ridiculous.
You think you can meet him whenever you want?
My spirit body...
No!
Gen!
Don't interfere...
Was that your power?
No wonder you could steal the Pearl.
Gen!
I'm fine.
Xiaohei...
You jerk!
Xiaobai.
Go inside.
But...
It's gonna be all right.
Take Xiaohei too.
Don't worry.
At worst I'll reveal myself.
So you won't give it up.
I've told you.
Master Lao suggested it.
Is this all you can?
I waited for a chance.
My well!
My vegetables!
My fruits!
Hidden money
↘
Fine tea.
Wake up, Grandpa!
Gen!
I'm fine.
Who are you?
Not the right time to mock me.
Over here...
Strange...
Is he hiding his strength?
We'll get him!
He doesn't take it seriously!
Don't hurry.
I'm about to be at advantage.
Can you see at all?
It's nothing.
Let's make a bet that...
Where is he?
What the heck are you doing?
It's raining.
So what are you doing there?
I sought shelter.
And the fight?
We're pausing.
Why?
Because I hate rain.
You can't stop a fight halfway!
We can fight inside as well.
It's bad for your health to stand in the rain.
Relax and have some tea!
How did we end up like this?
How can the rain fall so hard?
I'm worried about Piyu...
Don't be, he's safe where he is.
Ice boy.
I'm not "ice boy".
Are you afraid of thunder?
No way.
6 miles away a human got trapped under a collapsed building.
In which direction?
In front of us.
A pavilion!
I must help!
Be careful!
Sure!
How do you know?
I heard it.
Are you a spirit?
Yes.
You don't look like you're evil.
What's your name?
Diting.
Diting?
You know him?
Diting is a mythical spirit beast.
Wow...
Then you must be a good spirit.
But why did you attack Gen?
Are you not afraid, knowing what I am?
I'm not. Gen is a spirit too.
You actually knew it...
Are you not afraid of him?
Why should I be? He's my cousin!
Do you also know that...?
Ice breaking fire!
Who's there?
No time for this...
Where's the person?
Was he washed away?
Xuanli.
Did you make the ice breaking fire to test me?
Yes.
Don't worry.
I have rescued the human.
No secret is safe from you.
How did you find it out?
We simply know each other too well.
Why didn't you reveal yourself?
I live in seclusion now.
What's that sound?
Master Lao's magical sound transmitter.
Wow...
Is he that modern?
It's me.
Understood.
Meow.
Meow you.
Master Lao wants to see you two.
Why?
He's not after me, right?
No. It's about the Sky Pearl.
He realized it finally?
I don't know either.
We will see when we're there.
So you're in fact friends.
Yeah, we were just teasing each other.
It seemed quite serious to us...
Yeah, you were hit so hard you flew away.
You were after me?
Yes.
You did it for nothing.
I am a victim too.
So you will meet an immortal...
Can I go?
You can.
What? Really?
Master Lao will be glad to have company.
Can I take Xiaohei too?
Sure.
No need to tell her why.
And when do we leave?
Let's survive tonight first...
Don't be so happy...
It stopped at last...
But the flood won't go away for a while.
It's like this every year, we're used to it.
Grandpa.
You can go to Uncle San's place.
Please get Master Lao's sign for me.
You like him that much?
Let's go.
How do we get there?
Thank you for taking us.
Hold on tight!
I know!
Master Lao
If I knew this, I would have taken a ride...
Is this Master Lao the philosopher Laozi?
At least he was modeled on him.
He's not exactly like in the legends.
And is he powerful?
Of course.
Where does he live?
Not far from here.
Right?
Hold on.
Is this the place?
Yes.
But...
There's nothing here.
Follow me.
What...
What's this place?
Master Lao's mystical realm.
This is Blue Creek Town.
What's that?
The sky is so white!
Is this where the immortal lives?
Yes.
What do you think?
It doesn't look like where an immortal lives.
More like an ancient town.
It's so quiet here...
Is anyone living here at all?
No one's been here for a long time.
Too bad.
It's such a beautiful place...
Master Lao will be glad you like it.
We got to the gate!
Will we leave the town now?
How beautiful!
It's the Starry Night Lake.
Stirry Light Lake?
Yeah.
How come it's night here?
There's no real day or night here.
It's all controlled by Master Lao.
Can you see that mountain ahead?
That's Mount Laojun.
Master Lao lives on the top.
Those two cliffs are statues!
It's the "Got Light?" cliff.
It depicts the chance meeting of Master Lao and Fairy Qingning.
Oh...
How romantic!
Books everywhere...
Master Lao hasn't left this place for 30 years.
What a stay-at-home.
Don't say that!
And what's he doing for 30 years in here?
He's watching anime.
You have come finally!
Good day to you.
Xuanli!
It's a rare occasion you come to my place.
Not at all.
It's been a long time.
Are you Laozi?
I am.
For me you look like a child.
This is my economy mode.
Your clothes don't fit you.
It's more comfortable.
Your voice doesn't fit you.
My voice is just like I want :P
But I must maintain the image of a venerable wise man.
It's already gone.
Why don't you ever go out?
I have sworn not to leave this place for a hundred years.
Why?
I didn't want to talk about this.
Many years ago, a certain tragic event...
It's fine then.
Right.
Master, would you please sign this?
Sure.
Claim for damages caused by fighting?
It's... not what it seems like!
Let's just talk about our business.
Let us go to the inner room.
Xiaobai, wait for us here.
Okay.
Sorry for causing you trouble.
Diting, it's your fault!
None of my damn business.
I'm so sorry.
Now you're so polite...
What's this all about?
It would take long to tell.
Then say it quick.
400 years ago I placed
the Sky Pearl on top of the tower,
and swore that if someone can steal it, they can take it,
or bring it back,
and then I grant them a wish.
That's it!
So this happened.
You got it all?
Then why did I chase him?
Then why did he chase me?
I totally forgot about my vow.
Congratulations.
As the only one who could steal it in 400 years,
you must be a wielder of great skills.
You were careless.
It might be true.
But still, it couldn't have been easy for you to escape Diting.
Well, do you choose the Pearl or the wish?
Can they really sense it?
Most likely.
So this is Diting?
I don't think we can defeat him...
You just do your job.
Let us go ahead.
He's very fast!
Who are you?
Too late!
We did it.
And now
no one can stop us anymore.
It's all otaku stuff...
Stay with me aruite yukou ishikoro wo kette
Stay with me - let's walk on, kicking pebbles as we go
Yukisaki wa kitto kimagure demo
Our destination may be whimsical
Hana no kaori wo ryoute ni
But with the scent of flowers in both hands
kore kara deau kimi e to
I’ll carry it to the you I’ve yet to meet
Wait for me hanashi wo shiyou kata wo narabete
Wait for me — let’s talk, side by side
Hajimemashite wa gikochinaku temo
Even if our first “hello” is a little awkward
Mochiyotta hako aketara
When we open the boxes we’ve brought
Tsumekon da yume wo wakeaou
Let’s share the dreams we’ve packed inside
Mata ashita tte atarimae ni kawaseru hibi ga
The days when we can casually say “See you tomorrow”
Itoshikute hakanasugite
Are so precious and so fleeting
Omoi wa kitto kienai
Those feelings will never fade away
Sora wo nagareru kumo ni wa oitsukenai kedo
We can’t catch up to the clouds drifting across the sky
Ame ni natte hana wo tsukete kitto boku wo yonderu
But they’ll turn to rain, bloom into flowers
Kitto boku wo yonderu
And surely, they’re calling out to me